Bang!
You look happy!
Good morning! Yay!
Good morning.
Good morning. Good luck. High five! Yay!
Yay.
Good morning.
Well then.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll do my best.
Oh, no, I'm going to put on a suit.
Go for it.
Ah, ha.
Haa.
Don't take it off.
Oh, no.
Don't pick it up.
Today we all went to eat bread in the morning.
That's right.
Yuna said she always wanted to go there. Fresh truffles.
What was it?
It was delicious.
Something came.
Ah.
Good morning.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
An hour and a half in Japanese.
I'm so embarrassed. They can see this.
Why are you embarrassed by yourself?
We're both embarrassed.
Don't make it a pretext.
Good morning.
I'm not wearing any makeup.
Shall we go to the audience?
Let's go.
Wow.
Yes, it's OK.
Amazing.
Wow, wow, wow.
That's great.
What? What? What's this?
What? What? What?
I thought you wouldn't shake.
I thought I was safe.
I made fun of Yuniki's "I won't shake".
Hey, I just got the confirmation of the Barney Hart and Datessamba stunt.
What is it?
First of all, Datesamba starts, right?
The first thing that Daté Samba did was to say, "It's samba time, you guys.
Time.
Time for samba?
I'm invited by everyone.
I don't want it.
It's samba time.
What was that?
Are we almost done?
Where do we start?
It's starting.
This way.
Outside.
How do I get you into trouble?
I'll show you some lunches.
Here is today's bento.
It's a fancy bento.
I'm glad.
I'm waiting for the commercial.
Do it yourself.
Yes, yes.
It doesn't make any sense at all.
Today I, Mr. Taoki, and you all are going to have a sod-less showdown.
Today we have Mr. Ebinaka doing a live performance.
Hanke soddonless dance showdown.
You all dance, too.
One, two, three, four.
More and more. Come on, lift up your feet.
More. Still more... still more.
Lift your leg.
Lift them up.
When all the members are here, one of you will go in for sound check.
Please do.
On the defensive girl.
One more time.
Please.
BIG IN A ROUND! BIGGEST GIRLS NIGHT ROUND!
Miyake and Suda and the others, please.Miyake and Suda and others, please accept my best regards.
Best regards.
Please take care of them.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We are going to start check in.
We are going to start the first song of the two finals.
Dye my heart with fervor
Orange clouds riding the sunset
I hear a dream
Let's do another one later.
Please do.
Pitch is low.
Yes, sir.
Pearl, head, take my hand.
Overall, the group is still new to singing, so...
Yes.
I think the difference in piroli will show up soon.
I'll have them hold the burning towels, and from about the time they throw them, I'll try to break the pinks as it is.
I understand.
Press your hand like this, and then press it gently.
When you swing, push like this.
When you do the swing, push it like this, and there is no problem with the movement.
Two times this way.
Five minutes ago.
No, five minutes ago.
Who's drunk?
Five minutes ago.
Oh, no.
Four minutes ago.
Four minutes ago is not too much.
This is really funny.
Good. It's fun.
Let's all get excited.
Let's go.
Which one?
Idiot!
Shinju?
Ina!
Yuna!
Yuru!
Inatofu or Buchanan!
OK, I'm off.
That magical girl from Sriraday.
Bedrone.
Forelocks.
Kanegasaki. I'm off.
I'm going.
Congratulations.
Yoo-hoo!
It's the first time it's been shown to the public.
Hello.
We are now in the state of the fan meeting.
Yay!
And the Sendai pit.
Yes, I know. Sendai Pit, too.
We announced it on YouTube.
We announced it.
No one out? It starts tomorrow.
Looking forward to it.
It was fun.
The mike.
How was it on stage?
Stage debut.
Congratulations on your stage debut.
Congratulations.
It was fun.
The YouTube program was announced, wasn't it?
The response has been better than I expected, so the pressure is mounting.
So the pressure is really intense.
The pressure of filming.
It spreads like bread.
So, it was difficult to make it easy to shoot.
Yes, it was.
We had to make sure we were all breathing in unison.
Yes.
Please be aware of it.
At last, you are coming to the stage only for the performance.
I was nervous, but the stage is really big this time.
When I first saw it, I was a nervous backpack.
I've been on stage a few times for rehearsals and fami
I will do my best!
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Sh-sh-sh-sh!
Bento
I replaced the manager's because I prefer the singing ribs.
I'm going to win 100 fights in a row, one after another, and I can't lose.
I'll fight and fight and fight and grab it
I won't give up even if I fall down tens of thousands of times
More and more and more and more
I won't give up even if I fall a million times
I'll fight and fight and fight
I can do it!
He's crying. This person.
He's crying.
I heard he ate some chili peppers.They ate chili peppers.
The first one is the tastiest just to stir it up.
Thanks.
There's nothing we can't do.
Let's have fun! Let's have fun!
In this venue.
We are the best media in the world.
He's crying. He's crying.
He's crying. This person.
The moment Murray came.
At first, he just closes his legs.
Just a little more.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to go.
Actual start
Aaah!
Aah! I know! I know!
It's Matt. !!!!!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm 、、、、
I'm writing a semi-kei.
I'm going to go check it out!
I'm off to make a club!
~~~~~~~
I'm a naturopath, and I'm going to keep it up no matter what.
I'm going to live my life on fire.
I want to see you again
Vague summer
I wonder if a rainbow will appear
A puddle after the rain
Thank you very much.
Yes. The final performance of TOYOSPIT is over.
It's over!
Thank you, Yossu!
It's over~!
Thank you very much!
My mouth is shiny!
It's already 10:00.
Oh, my God.
I'll do my best for the recording tomorrow.
Thanks for your hard work.
I can't hit my chi.
Impossible, impossible.
I have chi.
Thanks for your hard work.
Disinfection.
Various ways to kill time.
It's already 10 o'clock.
Make it at 3 a.m. and go to Sendai.
Yes.
No, I think you're right.
Thanks for your hard work.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for your time.
Good work, sir.
Bye bye bye
Bye-bye.